Seitz, Peter Arbitration Files 5733
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Olean Tile Co., Inc. vs United Glass and Ceramic Workers, Local 151; Olin Corp. vs OCAW, Local 8-77, 1963-1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - overtime; call in - emergency. (Award Only.)
- Onion Enterprises vs. Sagittarius Broadcasting Corp. (Station WKTU), 1983 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  Issue: Demotion - management rights. RC, B, TR, SD, EX, Agreement.
- Onion Enterprises vs. Sagittarius Broadcasting Corp. (Station WKTU), 1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Onion Enterprises vs. Sagittarius Broadcasting Corp. (Station WKTU), 1983 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Pan American World Airways Inc. vs TWU, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Issue: Promotion - testing of employees; schedules of work - change of schedule - premium pay; rates of pay - overtime. (Award Only.)
- Pan American World Airways, Inc. vs TWU; vs. United Plant Guards of America; Pantasote Co. vs United Textile Workers of America (UTWA) Local 283; Penn-Dixie Cement Corp vs. CLGW Local 4, 1958-1963 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  Issue: Absences - holidays - rates of pay; discipline - discharge - sleeping on the job; discipline - discharge - plant rules - restricted area; discipline - discharge - carelessness and negligence; rates of pay - overtime. (Award Only.)
- Pennsylvania Department of Public Welfare vs. Pennsylvania Association of State Mental Hospital Physicians, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  Issue: Management rights - proof of illness - mental illness - termination of employment. TR, AN, RC, SD, EX, B.
- Pennsylvania Department of Public Welfare vs. Pennsylvania Association of State Mental Hospital Physicians, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania Department of Public Welfare vs. Pennsylvania Association of State Mental Hospital Physicians, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Pennsylvania Department of Public Welfare vs. Pennsylvania Association of State Mental Hospital Physicians, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Pepsi-Cola Metropolitan Bottling Co. vs IBT Local 830; Perkins Machine and Gear Go. vs IUE Local 268; Phelps Dodge Refining Corp vs USA Local 4355; Philadelphia Board of Education vs American Federation of Teachers (AFT) Local 3, 1959-1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft; rates of pay - time study; call in - failure to call in; insurance - payroll deductions - leaves of absence. (Award Only.)
- Philadelphia Board of Education vs AFT Local 3; Philadelphia Bulletin Co vs ITU, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  Issue: Premium pay - emergency - shutdown economic purposes; schedules of work - shift transfers. (Award Only.)
- Philadelphia Bulletin Co. vs. Philadelphia Newspaper Union, Local 16, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  Cancelled.
- Philadelphia Daily News vs IBT Local 628; Philadelphia Gas Works vs SEIU Local 686; Philadelphia Gear Corp. vs IAM Local 864, 1963-1977 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, excessive; assignment of jobs - rates of pay; vacations - shutdown - schedules of work - vacation scheduling. (Award Only.)
- Philadelphia Insulation Contractors Association vs. Asbestos Workers, Local 14, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia (Greater) Restaurant Operators' Association vs Local Unions 301, 111, and 115; Philadelphia Transportation Co. vs Transport Workers Union of Philadelphia; Pittsburgh Board of Education vs AFSCME Local 2924; Pittsburgh Steel Co vs USA; Plainvi, 1960-1978 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  Issue: Rates of pay - holiday; discipline - discharge - absences, excessive; grievance - timeliness; rates of pay; assignment of jobs - change in procedure; discipline - discharge - reporting absences. (Award Only.)
- Polymer Dispersion Industries vs UPIU Local 286; Polytherm Plastics, Inc. vs IAM Local 2189; Princeton Club vs Hotel, Motel and Club Employees Local 6; Printers League Section - New York Employing Printers Association, Inc. vs New York Typographical Union, 1960-1978 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  Issue: Rates of pay - overtime; schedules of work - change in schedule - management rights; discipline - discharge - improper job attitude; rates of pay - funeral leave - vacation; assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside classification. (Award Onl
- Providence Opera Theatre vs. American Guild of Musical Artists, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  Issue: Rates of pay - back pay awards. RC, B, SD, AN, EX.
- Prudential Insurance Co of America vs IWIU; Pratt and Whitney Co. vs UAW Local 405, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper personal conduct; schedules of work - shift transfers; layoff - bumping. (Award Only.)
- Pratt and Whitney Co. vs. UAW, Local 405, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Pratt and Whitney Co. vs. UAW, Local 405, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  Issue: Layoff - seniority - bumping as. RC, B, SD, EX.
- Public Service Electric and Gas Co. vs IBEW, System Council 4-2; vs. OPEIU, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension - work stoppage; suspension - tardiness. (Award Only.)
- Public Service Electric Gas Co. vs. United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry (PPF), Local 855, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  Issue: Schedules of work - contract interpretation. RC, B, SD, EX, TR.
- Public Service Electric Gas Co. vs. United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry (PPF), Local 855, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Publishers Association of New York (PANY) vs Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity (NMDU), 1959 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - change in procedure; shift preference - ability; transfer - physical disability. (Award Only.)
- PANY vs. NMDU, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  Issue: Schedules of work - shift transfer; overtime - equalization; absences - funeral leave - rates of pay; layoff - rates of pay; seniority - qualifications. (Award Only.)
- PANY vs. NMDU, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  Issue: Strikes, work stoppages; Classification of jobs - error in; seniority - physical disability. (Award Only.)
- PANY vs. NMDU, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  Issue: Seniority - return of supervisors to bargaining unit; rates of pay - disability; seniority - hiring; promotions - qualifications - past disciplinary record; rates of pay - overtime - bonus; layoff; financial irresponsibility. (Award Only.)
- PANY vs. NMDU, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  Issue: Demotion - absences; hiring - management rights; discipline - discharge - insubordination - improper job attitude; strikes, slowdowns, work stoppages; layoff - recall; assignment of jobs - contract interpretation; layoff - notice. (Award Only.)
- PANY vs. NMDU, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  Issue: Demotion - absences; reduction in force - management rights; assignment of jobs - change in procedure. (Award Only.)
- PANY vs. NMDU, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  Issue: Rates of pay - inequities; rates of pay - premium pay; assignment of jobs - change in procedure; promotion - promotional sequence; jurisdiction - assignment of jobs. (Award Only.)
- PANY vs. NMDU, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  Issue: Contract interpretation - job descriptions; overtime - schedules of work - reschedules; discipline - discharge - dishonesty; schedules of work - starting time change. (Award Only.)
- PANY vs. NMDU; vs. IBEW Local 3; vs. New York Mailers' Union No. 6; vs. New York Printing Pressmen's Union No. 2, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - outside work area; strikes - rates of pay; contracts - effect of strike - expiration; contracts; funeral leave - eligibility; strike, work stoppages. (Award Only.)
- PANY vs. New York Mailers' Union No. 6; vs. New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union No. 2, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - change in procedure; coffee breaks - fringe benefits - management rights; overtime - improper assignment. (Award Only.)
- PANY vs. New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union No. 2; vs. New York Typographical Union No. 6, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  Issue: Rates of pay - overtime; assignment of jobs - shift scheduling; rates of pay - holidays; discipline - discharge - carelessness and negligence - insubordination. (Award Only.)
- PANY vs. New York Mailers Union No. 6, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  Issue: Working conditions - crew size. (Award Only.)
- Purolator Products, Inc. vs. Employees' Union of Purolator Products, Inc.; RKO-General, Inc. vs. AFTRA; Radio Corp. of America (RCA) vs. IUE Local 103; vs. Association of Scientists and Professional Engineering Personnel, 1960-1977 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  issue: Layoff - seniority; rates of pay - wage hold back; discipline - discharge - application for employment - falsification; discipline - discharge - police record; layoff - recall. (Award Only.)
- RCA vs. Association of Scientists and Professional Engineering Personnel; vs. International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers (PTE) Local 241; Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, Inc. vs. IUOE Local 94-94A, 1972-1975 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  Issue: Layoff - unsatisfactory work; assignment of jobs - past practice; layoff - layoff pay; welfare funds. (Award Only.)
- Realty Services Co. vs SEIU Local 36; Reeves Instrument Corp. vs IUE Local 478; Remington Rand Division of Sperry Rant Corp. vs IAM Local 2104; vs. IUE Local 459, 1960-1979 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  Issue: Applications for employment - omission of information; rates of pay - increase; rates of pay - incentive pay; bargaining units. (Award Only.)
- Remington Rand Division of Sperry Rand Corp. vs Office Employees International Union Local 212; vs. IUE Local 459; Republic Aviation Corp. vs. IAM Local 1987, 1958-1961 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  Issue: Layoff - demotion; vacation - layoff; discipline - discharge - misconduct - strikes; classification of jobs - duties performed. (Award Only.)
- Republic Aviation Corp. vs IAM Lodge 1987, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - change in duties; classification of jobs - recall; classification of jobs - evaluation of job factors; classification of jobs - change in work assignments. (Award Only.)
- Republic Aviation Corp. vs. IAM Lodge 1987, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  Issue: Classification of jobs; layoff - recall - rates of pay; rates of pay - claim for pay of higher classification; seniority - date of eligibility; assignment of jobs - claim for pay of higher classification.
- Republic Aviation Corp. vs. IAM Lodge 1987, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  Issue: Recall - seniority; transfers - seniority; assignment of jobs - change of duties; classification of jobs - duties performed. (Award Only.)
- Republic Aviation Corp vs. USA Local 1331, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  Issue: Physical disability - termination of employment; elimination of jobs - transfers; rates of pay - guaranteed rate; assignment of jobs - change in procedure.
- Republic Steel Corp vs. USA Local 1331, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  Issue: Layoff - seniority; rates of pay - classification of job; rates of pay - discipline - restriction of production; assignment of jobs - seniority; assignment of jobs - past practice; working conditions - crew size. (Award Only.)
- Republic Steel Corp vs. USA Local 1331; vs. USA Local 1033; vs. USA Local 1375; vs. USA Local 6138, 1962-1964 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - assignment t o work outside classification; physical disability - termination of employment following; assignment of jobs - assignment of work outside unit; contracting out - sub-contracting - bargaining unit work; discipline -
- Republic Steel Corp. vs USA Local 1033; vs. USA Local 6107; vs. USA Local 3224, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences, excessive; discipline - layoff - absences, excessive; discipline - suspension - negligence and carelessness; rates of pay - time not worked; layoff - seniority.
- Republic Steel Corp vs. USA Local 2265; vs. USA Local 1200; vs. Local 2374; vs. USA Local 2265; vs. USA Local 1126, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Issue: Crew size - working conditions; schedules of work - assignment of jobs; layoff - seniority; assignment of jobs; reporting pay; premium pay - extended workweek; safety - protective clothing and equipment. (Award Only.)
- Republic Steel Corp. vs USA Local 1126; vs. USA Local 2265; vs. USA Local 1200; vs. USA Local 1098; vs. USA Local 2265, 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Issue: Seniority - assignment of jobs; seniority - return of supervisor to bargaining unit; working conditions - crew size; bargaining units - assignment of work outside unit; crew size - safety; bumping - seniority. (Award Only.)
- Resorts International, Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, Local 54, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Revlon, Inc. vs. RWDSU, District 65, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Issue: Arbitrability - Timeliness; falsification - time cards. (Award only).
- Rhodia, Inc. vs. OCAW, Local 13-622, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; applications for employment - falsification. (Award only).
- Rice Barton Corp. vs. USA, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Issue: Insurance - employer contributions. (Award only).
- Robertshaw-Fulton Controls Co., Bridgeport Thermostat Division vs. UAW Local 877; Robertshaw-Fulton Controls Co., Lux Time Division vs. UAW Local 1251, 1962- 1963 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - supervisors; schedules of work - change of schedule. (Award Only.)
- Rockbestos Co. vs. IBEW, Local 455, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  Issue: Discipline - substandard performance. B, AN, SD, RC, EX.
- Rockland, County of, and the Board of Trustees of Rockland Community College vs. Rockland Community College Federation of Teachers, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  Issue: Arbitrability - contract silence; rates of pay; seniority - assignment of jobs. (Award Only.)
- Roseland, New Jersey, Borough of vs. West Essex Policemen's Benevolent Association, Local 81, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  Issue: Arbitrability - estoppel; seniority - date of eligibility. (Award only).
- Royal McBee Corp. vs. UAW, Royal Industrial Union, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  Issue: Rates of pay - piecework vs. day work; seniority computation. (Award only).
- Royal Typewriter Co. vs. Royal Industrial Union, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Ryerson, Joseph T., and Son, Inc. vs. USA, Local 3746, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  Issue: Sick leave and sick pay - reinstatement after sick leave. (Award only).
- S and S Corrugated Paper Machinery Co. vs. IAM, District 15, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  Issue: Bargaining units - employees within bargaining unit; arbitrability membership in bargaining unit; bargaining unit employees within a bargaining unit. (Award only).
- S and W Fine Foods vs. Office Employees International Union, Local 153, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  Issue: Holidays and holiday pay - Saturday and Sunday work. (Award only).
- St. Joe Minerals Corp vs. USA, Local 3701, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  Issue: Discipline - suspensions; strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages - suspensions. (Award only).
- St. Louis Symphony Society vs. American Federation of Musicians (AFM), Musicians Association of St. Louis, Local 2-197, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  Issue: Absences - excessive; termination of employment. (Award only).
- San Souci Realty Corp. vs. BSEIU, Local 32B, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  Issue: Interest arbitration - contract modification. (Award only).
- Scarsdale, Village of vs. Uniformed Fire Fighters Association of Scarsdale, Inc., Local 1394, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Schaefer Brewing Co., The F and M vs. International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America, Brewery Workers Local Union Number 49, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  Issue: Vacation pay computation; Vacations - continuous service. (Award only).
- Schering Corp. vs. IAM, District 47, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Schwartz Agency, Mort vs. Screen Actors Guild, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  Issue: Rates of pay - back pay awards. (Award only).
- Scovill Manufacturing Co. vs. UAW, Local 1604, 1960-1963 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  Issue: Merit Increases and Merit Review discrimination; vacancies method of filling; Rates of pay - standards of production. (Award only).
- Screen Gems Stations, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 1212, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  Withdrawn. B, AN, RC. (No award).
- Seaboard World Airlines, Inc. vs ALPA; vs TWU, Air Transport Division, the Airline Mechanics and Stock Clerks, Local 504, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  Issue: Vacations - work in lieu of time off; contracting out - past practice; vacancies - seniority; contracting out - bargaining unit work; arbitration procedure - prior award, interpretation. (Award Only.)
- Seamless Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 338, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  Issue: Rates of pay - premium pay. (Award only).
- Sears, Roebuck and Co. vs. IBT, Local 107, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  Issue: Theft - company property; discipline - discharge. B, RC, SD. (No award).
- Seatrain Shipbuilding Corp. vs. MEBA, District 2, Shoreside Supervisors Union, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  Issue: Layoff seniority; arbitration procedure prior award, interpretation. (Award only).
- Shattuck Co., Frank G. vs. International Brotherhood of Firemen, Oilers and Maintenance Mechanics, Local 56, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Sherwin Williams Co. vs. Paint, Varnish and Allied Products Union, Local 1310, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  Issue: Overtime -assignment of jobs; rates of pay. (Award only).
- Signal Delivery Service, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 107, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; theft - customer property. (Award only).
- Simmons Co. vs. Simmons Elizabeth Employees Union, Local 420, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension; discipline - abuse of property. (Award only).
- Sinai Hospital of Baltimore, Inc. vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, District 1199E, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  Issue: Arbitrability - Jurisdiction; arbitrability - grievance procedure, failure to follow. (Award only).
- Singleton, Penny, Danny Thomas, and Jack Haley, Union Trustees vs. Ephraim M. Abramson, George A. Hamid, Sr. and Arnold Kaufman, Operator Trustees, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  Issue: Welfare Funds - rules for operation of plan. (Award only).
- Son Chief Electrics, Inc. vs. IUE, Local 212, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  Issue: Rates of pay - transfers. (Award only).
- Sound Distributing Corp. vs. IBT, Brewery Delivery Employees, Local 46, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; falsification - delivery records. (Award only).
- Soundscriber Corp. vs. IBEW, Local 1677, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  Issue: Termination of Employment - Inability. (Award only).
- Southern New England Telephone Co. vs. Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers, Inc., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  Issue: Rates of pay - reduction. (Award only).
- Sperry Gyroscope Co. vs. IUE, Local 450, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  Issue: Termination of employment improper personal conduct; Leaves of absence - sick leave. (Award only).
- Sprague Meter Co., Division of Textron, Inc. vs. IUE, Local 293, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; alcoholism, drinking and intoxication. (Award only).
- Spring-Perch Co., Inc. vs. USA, Local 2267, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  Issue: Reduction in force - seniority. (Award only).
- Springfield Gas Light Co. vs. International Union of District 50, Allied and Technical Workers of the U.S. and Canada, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  Issue: Arbitrability - waiver; discipline - discharge. (Award only).
- Squibb, E. R., and Sons, Inc. vs. OCAW, Local 8-138, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  Issue: Schedules of work - change of schedule. (Award only).
- Starleker Steel Corp. vs. USA, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; discipline - refusal of overtime. (Award only).
- Standard Brands, Inc. American Partition Co. vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Bound Brook, Local 813; Standard Brands, Inc. vs. International Union of Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of Am, 1962-1971 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  Issue: Rates of pay holiday pay; insurance beneficiaries; discipline discharge; union representatives and business discipline; Rates of pay - transfers. (Award only).
- Standard Gage Co. vs. IAM, Liberty Lodge 1678, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Standard-Thomson Corp. vs. IUE, Local 274, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  Issue: Seniority - assignment of jobs. (Award only).
- Star Expansion Industries Corp. vs. IBT, Local 445, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; absences, excessive. (Award only).
- Sterling Supply Corp. vs. IBT, Local 107, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; discipline - unauthorized use of company property. (Award only).
- Stouffer Management and Food Service, Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union, Local 217, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  Issue: Arbitrability - jurisdiction. (Award only).
- Stowe Woodward, Inc. vs. URW, Local 525, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 51)
- Stroheim and Romann vs. ACTWU, New York Joint Board, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; absences - excessive. B, EX, AN, RC.
- Suburban General Hospital vs. Pennsylvania Nurses Association, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  Issue: Rates of pay - cost of living allowance. RC, B, EX, SD, AN.
- Suffern Distributors, Inc. vs. Office Employees International Union, Local 153, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  Issue: Arbitrability - timeliness; termination of employment - discharge vs. quits. (Award only).
- Superb Light Alloys, Inc. vs. International Molders and Foundry Workers Union, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  Issue: Layoff - layoff pay. (Award only).
- Supreme Metal Fabricators, Inc. vs. Boilermakers' Lodge 5, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  Issue: Arbitrability - timeliness; insubordination - refusals in general. (Award only).
- Swedlow Plastics Co. vs. USA, Local 5585, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  Issue: Testing of employees - qualifications. (Award only).
- Syncro Machine Co., Inc. vs. UAW, Local 593, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - management rights. (Award only).
- Syracuse Area Distributors vs. United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America, Brewery Workers Local Union Number 49, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 59)
- T. P. Corp. vs. UTWA, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; improper personal conduct. (Award only).
- Tatko Brothers vs. United Stone and Allied Products Workers of America, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  Issue: Overtime - seniority. (Award only).
- Ten-Eighty Corp., WTIC AM-FM vs. AFTRA, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 62)
- Tenneco Plastics, Division of Tenneco Chemicals, Inc. vs OCAW Provisional Union No. 1, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  Issue: Overtime - cancellation; discipline - suspension. (Award Only.)
- Tennessee Coal and Iron Division, U.S. Steel vs. USA, Local 1733 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  Issue: Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages - discipline. (Award only).
- Tepper-Fields Corp. vs. UTWA, Local 281, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  Issue: Termination of employment - disability. (Award only).
- Terrell, St. John, as manager of Lamberville Music Circus vs. Actors Equity Association (AEA), 1959 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  Issue: Rates of pay - contract interpretation. (Award only).
- Texaco, Inc. vs. OCAW, Westville Local 8-638, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  Issue: Discipline suspension; Discipline - discharge; absences - excessive. (Award only).
- Tickle, Arthur Engineering Works, Inc. vs. International Molders and Foundry Workers of North America, Local 84, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 68)
- Time, Inc. vs. American Newspaper Guild, Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  Issue: Termination of employment notice; reduction in force management rights; Bargaining units - employees within bargaining unit. (Award only).